

Pablo Ripoll Torrejón

Software Engineer



# About me

### Hi there!

I am Pablo Ripoll Torrejón, Software Engineer currently working at ITURRI.

23 years old, I was born on March 30, 1998 in Encinasola, a small village in the Sierra de Huelva.

I currently reside in Seville, where I started my degree in Computer Software Engineering in 2016 at the Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería Informática of the University of Seville.



# Contact



+34 625 203 191



pablomarocho@hotmail.com



For more information, visit my website <u>here</u>.







# WORK EXPERIENCE

# ITURRI

## Software engineer

april 2021 - present (full time)

After finishing the internship, I was offered a full time contract, where I continue to perform the same role, including a number of larger projects with a little more responsibility.

#### ITURRI

#### Internship program

octobre 2020 - april 2021 (part-time work)

I decided to do an extracurricular internship during my degree and ITURRI was the company that offered me the opportunity. I joined the Organization and Systems department, where I was trained mainly in process robotization tools, Azure cloud services, as well as in the testing and development of various technical solutions.



#### **TRAINING**

## COMPUTER ENGINEERING - SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería Informática, Universidad de Sevilla

september 2016 - march 2021

I finished my Computer Engineering degree in March 2021 with an average of 7.9. I got 4 honors and obtained a grade of 9.2 in the Final Degree Project.

#### ENGLISH LEVEL B2

#### **APTIS**

february 2020

I obtained the B2 certificate in English issued by APTIS.

#### TECHNOLOGICAL BACCALAUREATE

I.E.S Eugenio Hermoso, Fregenal de la Sierra (Badajoz)

2014 - 2016

I obtained the title of Bachelor of Technology with an average grade of 9.76.



# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

If you want to know more about me, as well as the different technologies, and projects I have worked on, skills, etc, please go to <u>my website</u>, where you can get a more detailed and extensive version of my resume.